{
    "subject": "resource/Laurence_Marks_(British_writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/The_New_Statesman",
    "human_readable": "Laurence Marks (British writer) is notable for his work on The New Statesman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9525476694107056,
            "question": "Is Laurence Marks a British writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9505826830863953,
            "question": "Is Laurence Marks a notable writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7263492941856384,
            "question": "Who is Laurence Marks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246423959732056,
            "question": "Where did Laurence Marks work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6760843396186829,
            "question": "What is The New Statesman known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6508745551109314,
            "question": "What is Laurence Marks known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5536282658576965,
            "question": "What type of work does Laurence Marks do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5292482972145081,
            "question": "What is the name of the publication where Laurence Marks has worked?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45304107666015625,
            "question": "What publication is Laurence Marks associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4115010201931,
            "question": "What nationality is Laurence Marks?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laurence Marks (British writer) is notable for his work on The New Statesman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8704_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What publication is Laurence Marks associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8704_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the publication where Laurence Marks has worked?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8704_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work does Laurence Marks do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8704_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8704_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Laurence Marks (British writer) is notable for his work on The New Statesman.\" Specifically, several documents mention Laurence Marks as a comedy and television scriptwriter who has worked on projects like \"The New Statesman,\" starring Rik Mayall."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}